Michał Łachecki

Marketing Specialist at Brand24

Summary

An ecstatic, unconventional guy who doesn't like to be bored. Blend of confident communication style with a demonstrated ease in gaining trust across diverse audience, achieved from being a President of the European Law Students' Association ELSA Poland. Having extraordinary experience in leadership, management, project coordination and work in an international environment. During last five years despite being a part of one of the biggest students' association I managed to finish 2 faculties, worked part-time in the cinema, visited over 30 countries, created a big networking from over 43 countries and didn't go insane. That's why I am a real Risk-taker!

Experience

Marketing Specialist at Brand24 styczeń 2018 - Present

Lecturer at Dolnośląska Szkoła Wyższa luty 2018 - Present

I share my knowledge and insights on law in design and production of video games.

President at ELSA Poland

sierpień 2016 - lipiec 2017 (1 rok)

- Coordinated activities of 17 local chapters of association, especially in the field of external relations
- Executed external relations of association that includes contact, among others, with over 30 various firms
- Board Management (23 people)
- Cooperation with other NGO's (BEST, AIESEC, ESN, NZS, AEGEE, May, BCC)
- Managed association's budget of 150k EURO
- Delivered numerous presentations on ca. 20 events, audience ranged from 20 to 500 participants
- Marketing management

External contacts handled during term as President:

Institutions:

Constitutional Tribunal of the Republic of Poland Supreme Court of the Republic of Poland Supreme Administrative Court Polish legal Authorities

The Polish Bar Council

National Council of Judicial officers

National Bar Association of Legal Advisors

National Bar Association of Tax Advisors

United Nations Information Centre in Warsaw

Law firm and Consulting Companies:

EY- Partner of ELSA Poland

Allen & Overy - Strategic Sponsor of ELSA Poland

Deloitte - Strategic Sponsor of ELSA Poland

PZU – Supporting Sponsor of ELSA Poland

Gessel - Polish law firm

SMM Legal - Polish law firm

Olesiński i Wspólnicy - Polish law firm

Grzesiowscy - Polish law firm

Viadrina Kanzlei - German law firm

Rödl and Partner – International law firm

Norton Rose Fullbright - International law firm

Doktór Jerszyński Pietras – Pro Bono partner of ELSA Poland

DZP -Polish law firm

dLK - Polish law firm

President

sierpień 2014 - lipiec 2016 (2 lata)

- Board management (2 terms as a President of Local Group)
- Marketing management
- Executed external relations of association (local legal firms)
- Coordinator of National Council Meeting in Słubice (about 300 participants)
- Coordinator of dozen of local projects
- Creator of PR campaigns

Student Job at CineStar

grudzień 2014 - luty 2016 (1 rok 3 mies.)

- Customer service

Student Ambassador of University at European University Viadrina styczeń 2013 - sierpień 2014 (1 rok 8 mies.)

- Contact with University and Schools
- Training's for pupils

Vice President Marketing

sierpień 2013 - lipiec 2014 (1 rok)

- Marketing management
- PR management
- Fundraising

Student Ambassador at Deloitte Poland

wrzesień 2013 - czerwiec 2014 (10 mies.)

- Mediator between firm and students
- Project organisator(Deloitte Day, Day of personal development with Deloitte)
- Creator of PR strategy
- Brand establishment at University

Student job

listopad 2012 - maj 2013 (7 mies.)

Education

European-University Viadrina

Master of German and Polish Law, Master of Laws (LL.M.), 2015 - 2017

Dolnośląska Szkoła Wyższa

Master's degree, Big data, digital marketing & trendwatching, 2017 - 2019

Uniwersytet im. Adama Mickiewicza w Poznaniu

Master of Laws, Law, 2012 - 2017

Europa-Universität Viadrina Frankfurt (Oder)

Bachelor of German and Polish Law, Bachelor of Laws (LL.B.), 2012 - 2015

Activities and Societies: ELSA Słubice Viadrina Botschafter Ambasador Deloitte

Venos Studio

Stage vocals Diploma, 2008 - 2012

Honors and Awards

Motivationsstipendium von DAAD, Dean Award at AMU in Poznań

Michał Łachecki

Marketing Specialist at Brand24



Contact Michał on LinkedIn